Wilson Wu

Tech Lead



About me

I am currently working as a Senior Developer Level 2/Tech Lead in the Gaming Industry. I gained my master's degree in computer science in 2007. Worked as full stack developer from 2007 to 2009 by building intelligent building management systems with C++ and SQL. In 2009, I joined the gaming industry, became a front-end developer working on C++, ActionScript, JavaScript, and typescript. I created my first game engine in 2012, which became one of the most successful and longstanding game engines in our company. More than a hundred games have been developed on this engine, including many of our company's use today in 2022. Since 2019, I have been working on a new game engine focused on fast development and maintainability. For fast delivery, we build our engine on top of Cocos Creator to utilize its UI Editing and templating capability. For maintainability, we focus on reusability, unit testing and automation, aiming to use a single code base to drive a large number of games. Currently, the entire department is adopting this new engine. For some of our games, we are able to reduce our development time from 3 months to a week.

Specializing in Game Engine development. Proficient in software architecure design. Fluent in English and Chinese.

Skills

SOL

JavaScript/TypeScript			HTML5
CSS3	Node.js	Vue	C#/C++

legendary games. This engine is still in

Experience

Developer

Company A

since January 2016

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Frontend Developer

Company B

January 2015 - December 2015

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Trainee

Company C

March 2014 - December 2014

Making coffee and baking cookies.

Education

Master of Arts

March 2012 - December 2013

Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.

Bachelor of Science

March 2009 - December 2011

Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

Projects

best-resume-ever

🖺 🗀 Build fast 🛭 and easy multiple beautiful resumes and create your best CV ever! Made with Vue and LESS.



Contributions

best-resume-ever

🖺 🖨 Build fast 🧭 and easy multiple beautiful resumes.

https://github.com/salomonelli/best-resume-ever